traffichunt.com 2019-06-16

# TrafficHunt

### Privacy Policy

**WebTraffic LLC** doing business as **TrafficHunt** (referred to herein as “TrafficHunt”, “We”, “Us”, or “our”) is committed to protecting consumer privacy and to clearly informing users about the collection and use of information when using our Service. TrafficHunt is in the business of operating as an advertising network by connecting and bringing together Publishers (individuals and/or businesses who have their own websites, as well as traffic resellers) with Advertisers (individuals and/or businesses who need to advertise their products online) (hereinafter “Service”). As a result, we have put together this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect and use certain information. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what information TrafficHunt collects from individuals (referred to herein “you”, “your” and “user”) who access [www.traffichunt.com](https://www.traffichunt.com/) (the “Website”). This Privacy Policy also explains how We use and maintain that information.

### Login and use of the Website / Service

TrafficHunt will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location based information. However, to use Service, you must register and then log in. In order to register in the Service and to benefit from all the features of the Service, you must register for the use of the Service by setting up a user account and entering the following data:

  * \- Email address;
  * \- Full name (First and Last name);
  * \- Address;
  * \- Date of birth (Age verification);
  * \- GEO location.

### What we collect

We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with Service. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you.

Three types of data and information are collected by Us or shared with Us:

**Non-personal Information:**  
Which is non-identifying and non-identifiable information, without particular reference to the identity of the user from which such information was collected: When you visit our Website, information about your visit (e.g. how you navigate the site) may be collected and stored. This information may include the length of your visit, the date and time of your visit, the pages you look at and the sites you visit before and after leaving our site. It does not include personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing or email address or telephone number. We use this non-identifiable and aggregate information to better design our website and for the purpose of optimizing our services and/or business. We also may share this general non-identifiable information with our affiliates, suppliers, sponsors and advertisers.

**Personally-Identifiable Information:** Which is individually identifiable information that identifies an individual, or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, either alone or in combination with other information, or may be of private or sensitive nature.

As part of this voluntary registration, we may request contact information (such as name, mailing address, email address, etc.) and other data required for operating these services. We may only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily provide it. By voluntarily providing this personal information to us, by sending us a comment or suggestion, you will be consenting to the collection, use and distribution of your personal information by us for the purposes set out herein. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information and may access and enjoy many parts of our website without providing us any personal information.

**"Cookie”:** We keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a small entry-in text file, called a "cookie", on your hard drive. A cookie is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Cookies do not reveal personal information. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself such as email address, purchases and preferences. Cookies cannot read data from your hard drive.

The Site may contain electronic images known as “web beacons” which are also sometimes called single-pixel gifs. Web beacons may be used to assist in delivering cookies, allow us to count visitors to the Site pages and to deliver services via the Site. We may also include web beacons in email messages in order to determine whether such messages have been opened and acted upon. We do not tie web beacons to any PII you submit while on our Site.

### Use and sharing of information

For the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance all the personal data we process is located on servers within the USA. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. Your information that you provide us with will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to participate/benefit from Service. You can easily opt-out by emailing to us via [info@traffichunt.com](mailto:info@traffichunt.com).

We reserve the right to use your information: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for general Site administration purposes; (3) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; and (4) as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy. We do not share, sell or trade any of your information with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your information with our principles, officers, directors, members, employees, consultants, agents, subsidiaries or affiliates, or our subsidiaries’ employees and consultants (collectively “Related Entities”). Neither we nor our Related Entities contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your information.

In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your information will likely be among the assets transferred. We also reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

### Rights to Your Information According to GDPR

GDPR stands for the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679, which is a European Union law governing privacy and data protection for all residents of the EU. The provisions of GDPR can be also applied to how data is processed and verified (more on that later) outside the European Union. Generally speaking, the GDPR represents a new set of rules intended to empower the citizens of the European Union to control their personal information. In accordance with the applicable laws, users are authorized to access and modify their own data held by the companies, which includes data collection, ad tracking, surveys, cookies, location data, and every other bit of a user’s “digital footprint”. Users are also entitled to transmit their personal details to other organizations. The GDPR also enforces companies to determine their in-house data security policies.

At any time through the web interface provided as part of the Services or via contact us page you have the right:

  * \- to access your personal information that we hold;
  * \- to request the rectification of your personal information that we hold;
  * \- to request the erasure of your personal information that we hold;
  * \- to request to restrict processing of your personal information;
  * \- to object to processing of your personal information by us;
  * \- to request to transfer your personal information that we hold (e.g. data portability);
  * \- to file a complaint to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction; and
  * \- to withdraw any consent related to your personal information given by you.

We will process your requests to us within 30 days. We will also notify you within and a relevant supervisory authority within 72 hours from a breach related to your personal information that we hold. We have assigned a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who may be reached via dpo@traffichunt.com. Our DPO is tasked with ensuring that we acknowledge and abide by our data protection responsibilities. We will not store personal information for more than 6 months from the date of your last active session on the Site or for more than 6 months from the date of termination of an agreement between us and you (whichever is earlier).

### Security

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to authorized employees of TrafficHunt and the Related Entities. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any information transmitted to us or through the Site will be at your own risk.

### Intellectual Property

Intellectual property rights to the content of the Website, graphic design and codes are owned by TrafficHunt. Therefore, any reproduction, distribution, public communication, transformation or any other activity that can be carried out with the content of the Website without the written consent of TrafficHunt is prohibited. All trade names, trademarks or signs of any kind contained in the Website are the property of their owners and are protected by law.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please know that TrafficHunt may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. The updated Privacy Policy will be posted under the tab “Privacy Policy.” If you continue to use the Website after an amendment is posted on this Website, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of that amendment. Therefore, you should review this Privacy Policy each time you use the Website. You can tell when this Privacy Policy has been updated by checking the date at the bottom of such page. We also encourage you to print out a copy of this Privacy Policy for review and reference.

### Children’s Privacy

Our Site is not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years of age. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with PII we will take steps to remove such information. If you believe your child has provided TrafficHunt with personal information, such as by registering at one of Company’s websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us via: [info@traffichunt.com](mailto:info@traffichunt.com)

### If You Do Not Agree with this Privacy Policy

By visiting our Website and voluntarily providing personal information to the Website, You agree to the terms of the online General Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

Please note this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and does not apply to (and we are not responsible for) the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to individuals we do not employ or manage. If you do not want your information to continue to be collected and used as provided in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site again.

### What are your rights?

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer who will investigate the matter.

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or any general questions about the Program, please contact Our Data Protection Officer via: dpo@traffichunt.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. Alternatively, you may contact us at the address below:

WebTraffic LLC d/b/a TrafficHunt  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
36 Robinson Road, #13-01, City House, Singapore (ZIP 068877)

**Updated: May 16, 2018**
